# Luciano Nicolás Díaz



luchodiaz1995@gmail.com



+541159102957



linkedin.com/in/lucianonicolasdiaz



https://diazluciano.github.io/portfolio/

# **Summary**

I am a Full Stack developer with industry experience building websites and web applications. I specialize in .NET and have professional experience working with C# and JavaScript. I also have experience working with jQuery, CSS, HTML, SQL Server and React. I aim to specialize with React + .NET Core stack.

# **Experience**



## Full Stack Developer

Globant

May 2021 - Present (10 months +)

- Daily meetings with the Dev Team and Products Owners to report our situation (SCRUM, Jira).
- Maintenance and Development of a platform for the sale of advertising space (React + .NET).
- Unit Testing (Karma, Jasmine, NUnit, SonarQube).
- Work in POD, using Git for our changes and push to ADO respository.
- Comunication with our organization through Slack.

### Full Stack Developer

Time Solution Software

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

- Development and maintenance of Web Applications (Web Forms, Web Api, .NET Framework).
- Development and maintenance of Web Desktops (Windows Forms).
- Managment and development of Data Bases (MS SQL Server, T-SQL).
- Communication team through Discord and Trello.
- Work using Git for our code and push to a GitHub respository.

#### **Education**

#### **\*∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

University Technician in Computer Systems, Tecnología informática/Tecnología de sistemas informáticos

Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

#### \*UTN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

University Technician in Programming, Programación informática Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

## **Skills**

.NET Framework • ASP.NET • C# • HTML5 • CSS • JavaScript • jQuery • Jasmine Framework • Karma • NUnit